(Leonard:)Oh. My cute little tushy strikes again.
I'm serious. I've always had these plans.
I was gonna be in movies...
(Penny:)...and live this glamorous life,
and anything less than that...
(Penny:)...wasn't worth getting excited about.
- Those things can still happen.
(Penny:)Obviously, it's gonna happen.
A psychic at a bachelorette party told me.
(Penny:)Anyway, what I meant was
I shouldn't wait, you know?
(Penny:)I've got you, I've got Sheldon...
...and all these wonderful friends.
(Penny:)My life is exciting right now.
- That's a big deal.
- It is, isn't it?
(Leonard:)So does that mean we get to do stuff
like talk about cool shows...
(Leonard:)...or get dressed up in matching costumes
and go to Comic-Con?
(Penny:)Leonard, I had an epiphany, not a stroke.
Amy, I must say, I was skeptical at first...